快点
Hurry up.
停
Stop.
听着 我想亲手将你干掉
See, I want to just shoot you myself.
但我要顾及我的兄弟们
But I got to humor my brothers.
再过不久 黎明时分
In a couple of minutes, when the sun comes up,
我会给你这把手枪
I'm gonna give you this pistol.
现在 你愿意做件荣耀的事自行了断吗?
Now, will you do the honorable thing and kill yourself?
为什么我要这么做?
why in god's name would I do that?
羞耻和悔恨
shame and remorse.
屁话
bullshit.
不 你们
No, you all,
你们只是害怕成为谋杀犯
You just want to save yourselves from doing a murder.
爱上罗斯安娜 我一点也不羞耻
And I ain't ashamed of loving roseanna.
这么说他不愿自己动手
so he won't die by his own hand.
他愿意服毒吗?
will he eat poison?
去死吧
to hell with this.
把枪放下
guns down.
快
Now.
我说立刻
I said now.
照他说的做 不然你们的脑袋
do what he says, or I'll scatter your brains
将遍地开花
All over this place.
剩下的都跪到你哥哥旁边去
the rest of you kneel down there next to your brother
祈祷吧 你们的命全取决于它了
And pray as if your lives depend on it,
看他们心情好坏
On account they do.
你聋了吗 麦考伊?
Are you deaf, mccoy?
我说跪下
I said to kneel.
我不跪任何人
I kneel for no man.
并且我只对上帝祈祷
And I pray only to god,
不对你
Not you.
你很勇敢 吉姆・麦考伊
you're a brave man, jim mccoy.
你爸爸应该感到骄傲
Your daddy should be proud.
一切就绪 臭鼬头 放火
All right, skunkhair, torch it.
你知道吗 我们早该烧掉这个该死的地方
you know, we should've burnt down this shithole years ago.
喔!
Whoo!
这不关你的事
this is none of your business.
放开我!
get off me!
你这该死的蠢货 竟然自投罗网
you're a damn fool for riding into mccoy hands.
现在这都不重要了
none of that matters now.
罗斯安娜怀了我的孩子
Roseanna's carrying my baby.
她拯救了我
She saved my life.
我要和她结婚
I'm gonna marry her.
罗斯安娜怎么了?
roseanna's what?
这些你都知道吗?
Did you know about this?
约翰斯 她是麦考伊的人
johnse, she's a mccoy.
她背叛了自己的家族
She betrayed her own family.
迟早也会背叛我们
She'll betray ours too.
不是这样的
that ain't true.
你知道吗 我不接受
You know, I ain't...I ain't taking this.
不 你会接受的
no, you'll take it.
住手!
stop it!
你会乐滋滋地接受
you'll take it and like it.
快住手 求你了!
stop it, please!
昂斯 昂斯!
anse, anse!
嘿 够了
hey, that's enough.
够了啊  别太过了!
That is enough. That is...that is enough!
休想再动他一根汗毛 安德森・哈特菲尔德
You don't touch that boy no more, anderson hatfield.
你绝不能娶麦考伊的人
you will never marry a mccoy.
你胆敢离开这个家跟她走
You leave this house to go after her.
就别再回来
You don't come back.
现在 自己选择吧 立刻决定
Now, you make your choice. Make it now.
是走是留
Stay or go.
肯塔基州 黑莓湾
喔! 哇喔喔!
whoo! whoo-whoo-whoo!
到我了
I'm up.
上吧 上吧
come on, come on.
上 松鼠
go, squirrel.
加油 塞米
come on, sammy.
啊哈! 喔!
ah-ha! whoo!
兄弟们 我们赢了!
now we got a competition on our hands, boys!
来一瓶  罗伯特
one apiece. Robert e.
给
Here.
杰弗逊 杰弗逊
jefferson, jefferson.
这是家庭折扣
that's the family discount.
- 给我 - 不
- give me that. - no.
你已经有多少了?
how much you had already?
不 我一点也没有
no, I ain't had nothing.
- 给我 - 我没有
- give it to me. - I ain't had nothing.
别这样
stop acting like that.
别打我  别打我
quit hitting me. Quit hitting me.
嘿 罗伯特 拿着
hey, robert e., take over.
南茜
nancy.
你好 约翰斯・哈特菲尔德
hello, johnse hatfield.
嗨
hey.
最近可好?
How ya been?
还好
I been fine.
我应该早点跟你联系
you know, I should've called on you.
我真的不想伤害你们
I really didn't mean you no harm.
我只是...我想一切都是意外
I just...I guess what happened was kind of an accident.
我猜也是
I guess it was.
但你一点也不担心吗
But don't you worry about it none.
我满脑子都是罗斯安娜 一片混乱
I just been all messed up in my mind about roseanna.
她怎么样了?
How is she?
很不好
poorly.
医生说她咳得厉害
Doctor says she took down with a cough.
她一直在吐血
She's been spitting up blood.
他们说她的孩子或许保不住了
They think she might lose the baby.
保不住?
lose it?
或许能
or not.
谁说的准呢?
Who knows?
嘿 你能...
hey, will you...
你能代我向她还有孩子问好吗?
Would you tell her that I asked after her and the baby?
帮我这个忙吧?
Would you do that for me?
下次见到罗斯安娜...
I'll pass it along...
我会转告她
Next time I see roseanna.
安德森
Anderson
嘿 爷爷
hey, grandpappy.
一点也不好笑
that ain't funny.
是 是啊
yeah, it is.
嘿 别被他们吃干抹净了
Hey, don't let it eat you up.
嘿 说到吃
Hey, speaking of eatin',
你尝过腌秋葵吗?
Have you tried this pickled okra?
味道很不错
Delicious.
该死的辣椒
it's a damn pepper.
鼻炎犯了吧
bullnose red hot.
你个混蛋
you son of a bitch.
你要不是我兄弟 早就死翘翘了
If you weren't my brother, you'd be dead right now.
来吧 我们来跳舞吧
come on, now. Let's dance.
就在那 孩子
right there, son.
比赛还在继续吧?
this competition's still open, ain't it?
只要你不怕浪费子弹
if'n you don't mind wasting a bullet.
我还没废过一颗
I ain't wasted one yet.
你怎么打得中呀 雾眼?
how you gonna beat that, fog eye?
好运
Good luck.
嘿 嘿 别超线
hey, hey, toe the line.
你超过了那该死的线
You're over the damn mark.
耶 裁判应该注意到了
Yeah, judge should've caught that.
专注于你所做的 孩子
just do what you do, son.
他所做的只有失败
what he does is miss.
哦 盖
oh, cap.
你完全没打着
You missed complete.
不 他打中了
no, he didn't.
打中了上面的钉子
Hit the nail on the head.
就正正好好在中心
Right on the gol'dang head.
你看到子弹射向了哪里
you see where that went.
嘿 淡定 孩子们
hey, settle down, boys.
不 不 不 不 不 不
no, no, no, no, no, no.
这是射击比赛
this here is a shooting contest.
这是射击比赛 孩子们
This here is a shooting contest, boys.
起来
get up.
看呐
look at this.
看 麦考伊低下了头
Watch mccoy put his head down.
哈特菲尔德在发抖
hatfield's a-tremblin'.
恶魔昂斯不敢直视咱老头的眼睛
Devil anse couldn't meet the old man's eye.
兰德尔・麦考伊扭扭捏捏
randall mccoy looked away
像寂寞的女人第一次约炮
Like a lonely girl seeing a hard prick for the first time!
闭上你的狗嘴 哈特菲尔德
you watch your filthy mouth, hatfield.
可能会起纷争
might be some rowdy-do.
无论发生什么 科顿 你就待在这别动
Whatever happens, cotton, you stay right here.
别让马受惊
Keep these horses peaceable.
哈!
hah!
耶 麦考伊退缩了
yeah, mccoy flinched.
向后退了一步
Skipped off a step.
哈特菲尔德 拉屎拉裤裆了
hatfield, he shit himself.
你自己都可以闻到
You can smell it yet.
你说该怎么做 艾利生?
how'd you see it, ellison?
似乎大家都挺绅士
seems to me both men behaved gentlemanly.
如果谁让一步 大家就算了
If anyone looked off, they both did together.
我们走
let's go.
这是你欠我的
that is for owing me almost
我的传家宝小提琴你还欠我一美元
A whole greenback on my heirloom fiddle
一年了 你个偷窃的狗杂种
For a year, you thieving prick.
约翰斯是对的
johnse was right.
你打人就像老女人
You hit like a old woman.
或许你应该穿上裙子戴上女帽
Maybe we should get you a bonnet and a dress.
够了
no more.
我才是恶魔!
I am hell on earth!
你是该死的臭猪
you're a damn stinkhog.
够了
that's enough now.
交给你了 艾利生
you take him, ellison.
哈特菲尔德的人 别插手
hatfields, stay out of this.
快上
get in there.
来吧 巴德
come on, bud.
上 搞死他
come on, get him.
对 就这样
Yeah, that's the way.
你们还要多少?
How many more do you need?
让他坐在那儿
Let him sit there.
喔 我们之间还没结束
Aw, we ain't done with you yet.
喔
Aww.
啊!
Ah!
继续 那里 干掉他!
Go on, there, get him!
上你的舞蹈课去吧
Go take your dancing lessons.
跟跳舞似的!
You're going dancin'!
拿着
Take this.
捅死他们
Stick 'em.
艾利生!
Ellison!
坚持住 弟弟
Hold on, little brother.
一定要坚持住
Just keep holding on.
昂斯 昂斯
Anse, Anse.
在哪...
Where's...
科顿在哪?
Where's Cotton?
科顿 到这来
Cotton, come here.
要依法处理
Let the law handle it.
安心养伤
You get well.
我们会处理剩下的事
We'll look after the rest.
科顿 安慰下你爸爸
Cotton, you comfort your daddy.
我们可以回家了吗?
Can we go home now?
莉瓦西 扶他到屋里的床上去
Levicy, get him to a bed at the house.
约翰斯 盖 抬起他的脚
Johnse, Captain, get his legs.
抬他到马车上
Gonna get him in the wagon.
莉瓦西 去拿张毯子
Levicy, get a blanket.
把他抬到那上面去
Gonna get him up there...
他总是谋求和平
He was always angling for peace,
平息他人挑起的争端
Throwing water on fires that others started,
从不多管闲事 但现在却...
Letting people have their way, and now...
现在却可能因此丧命
Now maybe killed for it.
艾利生对你说什么了?
What did Ellison say to you?
他想见科顿
Asked for Cotton.
我们逮到他们了!
We got 'em!
警长拦住他们了!
Sheriff holed 'em up!
我们捉到麦考伊家的混蛋了
We got them bastard Mccoys.
昂斯 我们捉住他们了
We got 'em, Anse.
警长 你不能让他们带走我们
Sheriff, you can't let them take us.
昂斯 你弟弟怎么样了?
How's your brother, Anse?
还活着...
Still alive...
勉强来说
Barely.
我要你把这些犯人交给我 警长
I need you to hand over your prisoners, Sheriff.
我明白你的感受 昂斯
I understand how you feel, Anse.
但这些人在肯塔基州土地上
But these boys broke Kentucky law
违反了肯塔基州的法律
On Kentucky soil and are obliged
必须交由肯塔基州的法院审判
To be tried by Kentucky justice.
是吗
Yeah.
无论如何我都要带走他们
Well, I'll take 'em anyways.
昂斯 让我说几句
Anse, give me a minute.
我要将这整件事都记录下来
I want to go on a record about all this.
我正希望你这样做 法官
I wish you would, Judge.
向你的弟弟解释一下 不管他和你
Explain to your brother howsoever he and you
还有其他哈特菲尔德家的人什么感受...
And the other Hatfields feel...
我知道这很难受...
and I know that's awful...
这事都要通过法律途径解决
This business requires to be done legal.
警长 你得承认受害者是
Sheriff, you acknowledge the victim
西弗吉尼亚州的公民
Was a west Virginia citizen.
这是此案的本质所在
That's the essence of the case determinative.
也是西弗吉尼亚州法律存在的原因
That's why west Virginia law prevails.
现在 现在争论这个问题或是留到法庭上
Now, you can dispute the matter here or later in court.
作出选择吧 你这个婊子养的
It's your choice, you son of a bitch.
别到时候一个都没得选
You're likely to lose in either venue.
驾
Yah.
你们居然在我反对下强行带走这些孩子
You abscond with these boys over my strenuous objection.
冷静 冷静
Easy, easy.
该死
Damn.
他...他要死了吗?
He gon...He gonna die?
本来早就死了
Should've already.
噢 我的上帝
Oh, my lord.
收到托比亚斯・瓦格纳法官的指示
Obtained a directive from Judge Tobias Wagner
命令警长夺回孩子们并将他们
Instructing the Sheriff to recapture and restore the boys
送到他的合法羁押所
To his lawful custody.
警长
Sheriff.
法律...
The law...
狗屁不如
Ain't worth a bucket of spit.
他们...他们这是违法绑架
They...They were kidnapped illegal.
为什么我们不用同样的方法将他们绑回来?
So why can't we kidnap 'em back the same way?
不行 哈特菲尔德家族会严密看管他们的
No, Hatfields will have 'em heavily guarded.
有可能会变成一场血战
Could turn into a bloodbath.
亲爱的耶稣 他们都干了些什么?
Sweet Jesus, what have they done?
吉姆 你和佩里一起去派克维尔
Jim, you go with Perry to Pikeville
把这封信交给梅纳德警长
And get this letter to Sheriff Maynard.
卡尔文 我回来之前留在这陪你母亲
Calvin, you stay here with your mother until I get back.
爸爸 你不能去那里
Poppy, you ain't going over there.
我一个人去他不会伤害我的
Alone he'll do me no harm.
是爸爸
It's poppy.
哪里? 哪里?
Where? Where?
就在那里
Right there.
哪里?
Where?
就那...看见了吗?
Right...You see him?
是的 我看见他了
Yeah, I see him.
- 他是来救我们的 - 他来了 爸爸
- He's coming to get us. - There he is, poppy.
我手无寸铁前来 请求带走我的孩子们
I come unarmed to ask you for my boys.
我向你保证
You got my word.
我会把他们送上派克维尔法庭
I'll turn 'em over to the law in Pikeville.
你的孩子捅了我的弟弟
Your boys stabbed my brother.
不断地用刀捅他 然后开枪打死了他
They stabbed him over and over again, then shot him.
肯塔基州对谋杀罪的惩罚
Penalty for that's the same in Kentucky
和西弗吉尼亚州是一样的
As it is in West Virginia.
艾利生怎样了?
How is Ellison?
我祈祷他能痊愈
I pray he recovers.
你还相信祈祷这回事?
You still believe in praying?
我相信
I do.
好吧 那我们就让万能的主来决定这事
Well, then we'll leave it to the almighty.
如果我弟弟活下来了 你就可以带走你的孩子
If my brother survives, you can have your boys,
我们就让肯塔基州法庭来审判
And we'll let Kentucky law take its course.
如果他死了...
If he dies...
如果我弟弟死了
If my brother dies,
你的孩子在这里绝不会有命活到
Your boys will stay here not long before justice
法庭来裁判他们
Will be done on 'em.
我说什么或者付出什么
Is there anything I can say or give you
能让你改变主意?
That'll move you from that?
没有
No.
我想见见我的儿子们
I'd like to see my sons.
我不同意
I don't think so.
那就让他们母亲见见他们
Then let their mother see 'em.
我们会派人过去接她
We'll send for her.
恶魔昂斯・哈特菲尔德
Devil Anse Hatfield,
我真后悔那天救了你
I rue the day I saved your life.
愿上帝诅咒你的不朽的灵魂
May God damn your eternal soul.
兰德尔 或许吧
That might be, Randall.
但我不记得那天是上帝救了你的小命
But I don't recall God saving your ass that day.
我们救了彼此 因为那是...
We saved each other, 'cause that's...
因为那是男人在战争中该做的
'cause that's what men do in war.
这里发生的一切之所以变成这样
This all here, this all sits the way it sits,
都是我们自己的事 与他人无关
'cause of us and nobody else.
要是你觉得有必要再提一次上帝
If you feel the need to bring up God one more time,
是站在哪一边的话...
Whose side he sits on...
你绝对回不了家
You won't be making a ride home.
驾
Yah.
嘿
Hey.
我希望你和你家所有亲戚
I hope you and all of your kin
还有朋友和婴儿
And friends and babies
都来救他们 那我们就可以把你们一网打尽
Come and try to rescue 'em so's we kill you all at once,
就不用逼你们出来
Not drag it out.
吉姆
Jim.
闭嘴
Shut up.
什么 他要去哪里? 他在干什么?
What, where's he going? What's he doing?
他要抛下我们
He's leaving us.
什么?
What?
他要离开
He's leaving.
- 爸爸! - 爸爸!
- Poppy! - Poppy!
- 爸爸! - 闭嘴
- Poppy! - shut up.
爸爸!
Poppy!
爸爸 我们在这里!
Poppy, we're here!
闭嘴
Shut up.
爸爸!
Poppy!
你在干什么?
What are you doing?
在锯木板
Cutting the boards.
用来干什么?
What for?
以防万一
There's a possibility.
万一艾利生叔叔死了
There's a possibility of uncle Ellison dyin'.
吉姆说我们得准备一口棺材
Jim said we'd want a coffin.
你再锯木板试试看
Don't you cut no boards.
没我允许不准锯什么木板
I tell you when you can cut any boards.
知道了
Yes, sir.
? 前路漫漫 ?
It's a long road down
? 路漫漫 ?
Long road down
? 前路漫漫 ?
It's a long road down
? 路漫漫 ?
Long road down
? 前路漫漫 ?
It's a long road down
? 路漫漫 ?
Long road down
你煽风点火让我的孩子发起了这场争端
You gave out my boys purpose to that fight.
你最好尽你的职责带他们回来
Now you better do your job and get 'em back.
我们刚组建了一支武装队伍
We just have to get up a posse.
我们这里还有托比亚斯・瓦格纳法官
We have a written finding here
的一份书面说明
from Judge Tobias Wagner
说赋予你合法权力进入西弗吉尼亚州
Stating you're legally entitled to enter west Virginia
追捕他们
In hot pursuit.
西弗吉尼亚州的最高统治者
West Virginia's sovereign
还有遍布的武装起来的哈特菲尔德族人
And has armed Hatfields swarming all over.
后果你承担不起
You cannot abide by this.
如果艾利生・哈特菲尔德死了
If'n Ellison Hatfield dies,
恶魔昂斯会杀了我的儿子们 他说到做到
Devil Anse has so much has said he'd kill my sons.
艾利生死了 你的儿子们就是凶手
Ellison dies, your sons are murderers.
你又树敌了 警长
Just made some enemies, Sheriff.
滚开
Get out of my way.
加勒特牧师
Reverend Garrett.
安德森・哈特菲尔德队长派我来接你
Captain Anderson Hatfield sent me to fetch you.
他答应过兰德尔
He promised Randall.
艾利生?
Ellison?
已渡过约旦河 与天使共唱歌
Passed over Jordan singing with the angels.
噢 我的天啊
Oh, dear god.
妈
Ma.
我来接你去见你的孩子们
I'm to fetch you to your boys.
他们在哪?
Where are they?
他们在一个安全的地方以便他们
They're in a safe place where they can visit
与母亲相见
With their mother.
只能带她去
I'm to bring only her.
我向你保证
I gave my word.
骑马去派克维尔
Ride to Pikeville.
告诉你父亲我在哪里 发生了什么事
Tell your father where I am and what has happened.
好的 妈妈
All right, ma.
我是来见我儿子们的
I've come to see my sons.
他们在里面
They're inside.
昂斯 你能这么做真的很有基督教徒的风范
it's very christian of you to do this, anse.
留着圣会上再说吧 牧师
save it for your congregation, preacher.
求你了 哈特菲尔德队长
please, captain hatfield.
让我带他们回肯塔基
Let me take 'em back to kentucky with me.
求你了
Please.
你会带他们回去的
you'll get 'em back.
我只能承诺你这么多
That much I can promise you.
妈妈
mama.
我从家带了点吃的
I brought some food from home.
爸爸来了吗?
is poppy here?
他来了吗?
Is he coming?
我从院子里的果树上摘了些苹果 还带了奶酪
I've got apples from the yard tree and cheese,
你喜欢的那种 巴德
The one you like, bud
你姐姐烤的面包
Bread your sister baked
爸爸来了吗?
is pop comin' back?
还有鸡肉
some chicken.
- 列王记上卷中说 - 等会儿 教士
- from the first book of kings - hold on, reverend.
妈妈 我们...
mama, we...
我们看见爸爸离开了 他什么时候过来
We saw poppy riding away. When's he coming back?
他什么时候带我们离开这里?
When's he getting us out of here?
你想象不到生孩子时
you can't imagine the pain that comes
的那种疼痛
With giving birth to a child.
但我一次次迎来那种疼痛
But I welcomed that pain over and over
因此 我才拥有了你们每一个
So that I might have each of you.
我爱你们
I love you all
直到永远
And will always love you.
那爸爸呢
but what about poppy?
他也会永远爱你们
he will always love you too.
我是说...
I meant...
"将来躲避哈薛之刀的"
"Any who escape the sword of hazael"
出自《列王记》上卷19:17-19:18
"必被耶户所杀"
"Will be put to death by jehu."
"躲避耶户之刀的"
"And any who escape the sword of jehu"
"必被以利沙所杀"
"Will be put to death by elisha."
"但我在以色列人中为自己留下七千人"
"But I shall spare 7,000 in israel."
"是未曾向巴力屈膝的"
"All the knees that have not bent before baal."
"未曾与巴力亲嘴的"
"All the mouths that have not kissed him."
好了
all right.
就在山核桃树那吧
hickory tree there.
把他们捆紧点
tie 'em tight now.
约翰斯
johnse.
Johnse.
太紧了吗?
is that too tight?
开枪的时候
you're shooting phamer there
你负责费默尔
When the time comes.
早知今日何必当初呢
you reap what you sow.
你打托尔伯特
you're shooting tolbert.
好
mm.
先打托尔伯特
tolbert first.
你打巴德
bud.
你们知道接下来要发生什么吗?
You boys understand what's gonna happen here?
明白为什么要这么做吗?
You understand why?
做好准备
Make yourselves ready.
瞄准
aim!
放下你的仁慈
Harden your hearts.
"神啊 你必须要杀戮恶人"
"Surely thou shalt slay the wicked, o god."
出自《圣经》旧约全书 诗篇139:19-139:22
"所以你们好流人血的 离开我去吧"
"Depart from me therefore, ye bloody men.
"耶和华啊 恨恶你的"
"Do not I hate them"
"我岂不恨恶他们吗?"
"that hate thee, o lord?
"我切切地恨恶他们"
"I hate them with perfect hatred.
"以他们为仇敌"
I count them mine enemies."
你的弑兄仇人也是我的杀父仇人
same family that killed your brothers killed my pap.
总有人得做点什么
Somebody ought to do something about it.
没见着你姐姐
I don't see your sister.
罗斯安娜生病了
roseanna's ailing.
还待在贝蒂阿姨那里
Still laid over at aunt betty's.
哪都去不了
Can't travel none.
她流产了吗?
she lose the baby?
没有 她生了个女孩
no, it come, a girl,
但那孩子身体很弱
But it's sickly.
快死了吗?
likely to perish?
我祈祷她不会
I pray not.
但应该快了吧
but likely.
可能吧
likely.
孩子的爸爸是约翰斯・哈特菲尔德...
baby's daddy, johnse hatfield...
人们都说他也参与了残杀你哥哥的事
Folks are saying he was amongst them that killed your brothers.
我祈祷他没有
I pray he wasn't.
好像是真的
likely was.
那只是好像
likely.
托尔伯特...
tolbert...
费默尔...
Phamer...
还有巴德...
And bud...
他们遭遇了如此的
Having been handled with such
不公正和残忍的谋杀
Manifest injustice and cruelly murdered,
当他们站在上帝面前
When they stand before the lord,
上帝会洗去他们的罪恶
He will wash away their sins
带他们去乐土
And take them to the promised land.
人们忘记
people forget
哈特菲尔德家的人也杀了我爸爸
Hatfields killed our pap too.
一位从战场归来的正直士兵
Honest soldier coming home from war
什么坏事也没做
Doing no harm.
那是哈特菲尔德家欠下的另外一笔血债
That's another item goes on hatfield's account...
闭嘴 过来
shut up. Come on.
虽然已经过去很久了
which reckoning is past due,
证据也不容易找到
Which bill needs collectin'.
过来
come on.
我接受捐赠和善款
I'm accepting donations,
用于抚慰那些被嗜血的哈特菲尔德家族
Reward money for the capture or killing
俘虏或杀害的亡灵
Of the murderous hatfields.
我代表麦考伊家族感谢你
Mccoy family thanks you.
要让罪人得到惩罚
Do not let this atrocity go unpunished.
耶稣会赞赏你和你家人
Jesus will be smiling on you and your family.
谢谢 谢谢
Thank you. Thank you.
你不应该再待在这了
it ain't fitting you remain here
你已经坐在这好几天了
Just sitting days on end.
我知道他的仇已经报了
I know he's revenged.
我想我爸爸
I miss my daddy.
我弟弟总是以事业为重
my brother was always about the work of life.
他...
He'd...
他不会
He'd not...
他不会想看到你对着他的坟墓如此消沉...
He'd not want you lingering about his remains...
特别是...还有很多活等着你去干
Not when...not when there's chores to do.
镇子上太多生面孔了
a lot of strange faces in town.
都是缉凶猎人 兰德尔
man hunters, randall,
他们来是为了给你儿子讨个公道
Here to bring your sons' killers to justice.
他们来才不是为了这个
they ain't here for justice.
他们是冲着我们悬赏奖金来的
They're here to try and collect the bounty we're offering.
女士
Ma'am.
这是恶魔昂斯・哈特菲尔德的伐木工厂吗?
this here devil anse hatfield's loggin' enterprise?
恶魔昂斯明早才回来
devil anse won't be back till tomorrow mornin'.
如果你想找工作 他只雇佣熟人
If you're looking for work, he only hires men he know:
邻居 或者亲戚
His neighbors, his kin.
好吧 我有笔生意要给你做
well, right now, I believe I got business with you.
你什么意思?
what's that?
汤姆 你头发里有一撮可笑的白毛
you got that funny streak of white in your hair, tom.
我猜 所以人们才叫你臭鼬头
Guess that's why folks call you skunkhair.
我的朋友才那么叫我
my friends call me that.
汤姆 怪不得我们做不了朋友
well, no reason we can't be friends, tom.
别生气
Don't get testy.
我只是做好本职工作
I'm just doing my job.
你可是被通缉的 臭鼬头汤姆・华莱士先生
You got a prize on your head, mr. Skunkhair tom wallace.
你找错人了 我什么也没做过
you got the wrong man. I didn't do nothin'.
肯塔基州法庭可不是这么说的
kentucky courts say otherwise.
肯塔基州在拖轮河那边 你迷路了吧
you must've crossed the tug and got lost.
这里是西弗吉尼亚
This here west virginia.
我没找错地方 汤姆
I'm in the right place, tom.
麦考伊家已就他家三个孩子的谋杀
Mccoy family's gettin' indictments for them
提起了诉讼
That murdered their three boys,
已经贴出悬赏告示了
Already posted rewards.
搞什么鬼呢?
what the hell?
悬赏多少?
How much?
具体数字我记不清了
I don't recollect exact.
只是抓你的话肯定没多钱
Couldn't be more than two bits or so for you.
你这个狗娘养的
you son of a bitch.
把它关上
shut it down.
然后拿下来
Take 'em off.
好
all right.
嘿 塞尔柯克 过来
hey, selkirk, come here.
过来呀 你去哪了?
Come here. Where you been?
你喝酒了?
You been drinkin', hmm?
没有 先生
no, sir.
没有?
no?
那你睡觉了?
You sleepin'?
是的 先生
yes, sir.
扣你25美分?
I'ma hold back 25 cents?
是的 先生
yes, sir.
25美分?
25 cents?
昂斯
Anse!
昂斯!
他们把他头皮给剥了 就像印第安人做的那样
they scalped him, like indians done it.
我俩打小就是好朋友
He's my best friend since we was little.
吉姆
Jim.
他是我最好的朋友
He was my best friend.
兰德尔・麦考伊干的
randall mccoy done this.
觉得这下我们就扯平了
thought we'd leveled the scales.
昂斯舅舅 我在伐木场发现了这些
uncle anse, I found these in the logs
放在臭鼬头的尸体下
Underneath skunkhair.
悬赏七百五美元杀你
$750 for you.
看看你是怎么当匪领的
Seeing as how you was the outlaw leader.
到底怎么了?
what in tarnation?
我在其中吗 弗伦奇?
Am I in there, french?
拉克 我中招了 你也一样
well, I'll be damned, lark, you and me both.
他们连我也要抓
they're after me too.
见鬼 塞尔柯克你的命居然比我值钱
hell, selkirk, you're worth more than me,
你是麦考伊背叛者
Mccoy defector that you are.
六百美元?
$600?
那是沃尔叔叔
that's uncle wall.
沃尔叔叔根本没参与那场射杀
uncle wall wasn't even in that shootin'.
这下一发不可收拾了
this is out of hand.
一群贪钱的逃兵和吸血鬼
greedy bushwhackers and bloodsuckers by the dozens
正在到处追杀我们
Are gonna come after us.
随身带好你们的枪
just keep your guns handy.
盖
Cap.
在 先生
yes, sir.
好好照料臭鼬头
take care of skunkhair here.
其他人都回去工作
Everybody else get back to work.
利亚斯
'lias.
- 快点 - 昂斯 跟你说几句
- come on. - anse, a word.
我觉得我们应该储存一些物资和弹药
Reckon we ought to stock up on supplies and ammo.
但如果武装队来的话 我们就把他们引进山里
We need to take to them hills if a posse comes.
没人比我们更熟悉这些山了
nobody knows these hills like us.
沿岸都设上放哨的
Set up lookouts along the tug.
他们再也不能出其不意地抓住我们了
We won't get caught unawares again.
嗯
uh-huh.
罗斯安娜近况如何?
what do you hear of roseanna?
我曾经有个女儿叫做罗斯安娜
I once had a daughter roseanna,
如今我已经当她死了
Who's now dead to me.
莎莉过得如何?
How's sally holding up?
糟糕透了 你想说什么?
poorly. How would you expect?
女人总是特别受照顾 不是吗?
women are fortunate to enjoy special consideration, hmm?
如果每次悲剧发生后
If I curled up in a ball
我都像刺猬一样蜷缩成一团
every tragic turn of events,
那么我什么也做不好了
I'd never get any work done.
不要再像个白痴一样说话
quit talkin' like an imbecile.
你没有体会过丧子之痛
You never lost your sons.
克莱因先生?
Mr. Cline?
对不起 我们现在很忙
not now. We're busy here.
再忙也得把二百五十美金的赏金付给我
not too busy to pay me the $250 bounty owed me
臭鼬头汤姆・华莱士先生的
On mr. Skunkhair tom wallace.
你们要看他的耳朵吗?
Should I have brung his ears too?
把那令人反胃的东西拿走
put that abomination away.
我要赏金
I'm owed the bounty.
我们没有提出这种要求
there were no conditions imposed.
我们不是野蛮人
we are not savages.
我们的职责是将野蛮人绳之于法
It is our duty to bring the savages in for justice.
请不要再残忍地对待他们的尸体了
avoiding unnecessary wear and tear on their corpses.
我差一点就逃不出西弗吉尼亚州了
had to get me out of west virginie quick.
我的马承受不了多一个尸体的重量
Couldn't strain my horse toting a whole carcass.
你叫什么名字?
what's your name?
弗兰克・菲利普斯.
frank phillips
你就是那个传说中的"恶人弗兰克"?
you the one they call "Bad frank"?
不要当面这样称呼我
not to my face.
不要再有第二次
And not twice.
请不要再来领取更多的赏金了 菲利普斯先生
do not come back for more reward money, mr. Phillips.
我们家族向来不喜暴力行事
I will not be a party to atrocity.
我们申请到了关于谋杀案的诉求书
any event, we got our indictments
我们会委派代表去拖轮河对岸
Against the murderers, and we're sending deputies
负责此事
Across the tug.
毫无疑问 他们会妥善处理的
No doubt they'll handle things just fine.
女士
Ma'am.
我想见见罗斯安娜
I'd like to see roseanna.
见见我们的孩子
See our baby.
即便她现在身体健康
even if she weren't too sickly,
她也不愿意见到杀死自己亲兄弟的凶手
She'd not want to see the murderer of her brothers.
我没有...我没有杀死他们
I didn't...I didn't murder 'em.
我当时确实举枪了
I raised my rifle.
但我的子弹从他们头顶飞过
I shot over their heads.
不信你可以问问亚历克斯・梅塞尔
You can ask alex messer.
我为我和罗斯安娜 还有我们的孩子
I built a cabin for me, roseanna,
建造了一个小木屋
And the baby to live at.
它真的很漂亮 窗户上面还贴了油纸
It's a--it's a real nice one with an oilpaper window.
小木屋是为了你的酿酒事业建的吧
you built a cabin for your whiskey business
然后就可以跟那些妓女鬼混了
And to consort with whores.
他妈的
god damn it.
我千辛万苦到这里来
I took a chance coming here.
他们还悬赏捉拿我
They got a reward out for me.
求您了
Please.
一个男人...
A man...
他有权利见自己的孩子
A man's got a right to see his own child.
在这里你什么权利都没有
you got no rights here.
快点从我面前消失
Now, get yourself off my porch and gone.
我有权利!
I got my rights!
我告诉你!
I'm tellin' you that!
他妈的!
God damn it!
驾
Come on, girl.
看到他了吗?
you see him?
You see him?
看到他了吗?
是的
yeah.
看到他了
I got him.
开枪
shoot him.
小点声 帕里斯
just be quiet, parris.
打中了吗?
did you get him?
没有
no.
表明身份
identify yourself.
再说一次 表明身份
I said identify yourself.
赏金猎人
bounty hunters.
最下三滥的那种
Worst kind of trash.
盖 拿出纸笔
cap, get your paper and quill.
是时候给兰德尔・麦考伊警告了
Time to put randall mccoy on notice.
在镇子外面几英里的地方发现这些绑着的马
found these horses ground-tied a few miles out of town.
我想应该把它们带回来给警长大人
Figured I'd bring 'em in for the sheriff.
上面有一封信
Letter pinned on there is addressed
是给克莱因律师和麦考伊先生的
To the lawyer cline and you, mr. Mccoy.
"我的名字是纳特・哈特菲尔德"
"My name is nat hatfield."
"我不是一个人在战斗"
"I am not one individual but many."
"在此警告"
This is as good as a confession.
"如果你们闯入我们的领地"
"We hereby notify you that if you invade our state
"抓捕或杀害任何一个哈特菲尔德人"
"To take or kill hatfields, "
"我们将追查到底"
"we will charge it to you."
"要你们血债血偿"
"Your hides will pay the penalty."
恶魔昂斯・哈特菲尔德威胁要杀死我们
devil anse hatfield is threatening to kill us,
就像他对这些人所做的一样
Like he done these men.
有书信为证
We got it in writing.
我们需要您的帮助 米勒先生
We appreciate your help, mr. Miller.
让我先把这些马交给警长大人
let me get these horses over to the sheriff.
嘿 科顿 再给我们拿一瓶
hey, cotton, give us another bottle.
科顿 再来一瓶
Cotton, give us a bottle.
我非常爱约翰斯・哈特菲尔德
I love johnse hatfield so much.
他怎么就看不到呢?
Why don't he see that?
因为你是个婊子
on account of you're a whore.
那也比麦考伊家的婊子强
better than some mccoy bitch.
盖 把威士忌放下
cap, put down the whiskey,
假装需要解手
Make like nature calls.
明白了吗?
Get my drift.?
好了 我去解个手
all right, I'm gonna find me a tree to water.
很好
that's good.
你知道吗 我认识这个家伙已经三十年了
You know, I knew this boy once 30 years ago.
他可以把手放在火上
Could hold his hand over that fire
整整两分钟 都不怕疼
For two minutes and take the pain.
你知道他是谁吗 淡毛科顿?
Do you know who that boy was, cotton top?
就是你的叔叔 老吉姆・万斯
That was your old uncle jim vance.
不是吧
no.
是的 不骗你
yes, god's truth.
威廉 "盖" 哈特菲尔德
william "Cap" Hatfield.
什么事?
yeah?
把裤子系上 你个下流胚
button your dick, you vulgar bastard.
我正式逮捕你
I'm arresting you
因为你涉嫌谋杀托尔伯特 费默尔和...
for the murder of tolbert, phamer, and...
米勒?
miller?
米勒 快点 醒醒
Miller, come on, wake up.
又一个准备帮你们解决事情的代表?
Another one of your deputies what's gonna fix things for ya?
望远...
a tele-scop...
镜 镜
scope scope.
是个望远镜
it's a telescope.
望远镜
tele-scope.
和枪配备使用的 最新产品
for a gun, latest thing.
一百码外的物体
You shoot a target at 100 yards,
射起来就跟二十五码外的一样容易
makes it the same as 25.
开玩笑吧?
you joshin' me?
二十五码的距离百发百中
Hard to miss at 25 yards.
是的
yep.
六个月之前才订货的
Ordered it near six month ago.
推船最近才把货送到
Just arrived by push boat.
好好看看 哥们
Take a look, little brother.
的确物有所值
That is one fine purchase.
我计划用它来杀恶魔昂斯
I figure to use it on old devil anse.
嘿 把它给我
hey, give me that.
快点
Come on.
拿着
Take that.
看到他了吗?
you see him?
你到后面去
get on the ground behind me.
屏住呼吸
Don't even breathe.
这次肯定把你拿下
I got you this time.
哦 上帝
oh, god.
嘿 昂斯!
Hey, anse!
我们这次干掉一个真正的麦考伊家的人啦!
I do believe we got ourselves a real mccoy!
盖一枪打死他们啦!
Cap done shoot 'em dead!
你救了你爸爸一命
You saved your pappy.
我以你为豪 孩子
I'm proud of you, son.
你干得不错 孩子!
You are good, boy!
妈妈 你确定一点不吃吗?
mama, are you sure you won't eat some?
不 谢谢你 亲爱的
no, thank you, sweetheart.
我很好
I'm fine.
你有什么事情要告诉我?
there's something you've been wanting to tell me?
说吧?
What is it?
你的侄子帕里斯被杀了
your nephew parris has been killed.
哦 天啊
good lord.
可怜的帕里斯
Poor parris.
我们该行动起来了 兰德尔
got to do something about it, randall.
每周死去的侦探和家族成员越来越多
Got more detectives and family coming back dead every week.
你不能再畏手畏脚了
You can't keep poking a mad bear with a twig
事态只会越来越糟
And making it madder.
我们得有次大行动
We need a big stick,
得有人替我们讨回公道了
Someone prepared to execute our indictments.
爸...
pa...
让我去吧
Let me do it.
让我去收拾那些杀死我哥哥们的凶手
I'll get my brothers' killers.
我可以协助他
I'll be his right hand.
我知道如何用枪 爸爸
I can fire a gun, pa.
我欣赏你们的勇气 孩子们
I appreciate it, boys,
不过目前唯一一次
but the only success we've had
成功捕获逃犯
In capturing any of our fugitives
还是恶人弗兰克做的
Has been with bad frank.
我不喜欢那个男人
I do not like that man.
那个男人是个野蛮人
That man is a savage.
只有他可以胜任这个任务
he's the only one equal to the task.
这个恶人 这个野蛮人
can this bad man, the savage,
可以让我的孩子们死而复生吗?
Can he bring me my boys back?
有人来看你啦
we got a paying customer for ya.
再见 南茜小姐
Bye, miss nancy.
想要见你一面简直
easier seein' president chester a. Arthur
切斯特・艾伦・阿瑟为美国第二十一任总统
比见切斯特・艾伦・阿瑟总统还难
Than passing through these woods to get your 'shine.
你来这里做什么 南茜?
what you want, nancy?
给我的哥哥买一些威士忌作为生日礼物
purchasin' whiskey for my brother's birthday.
我听说你去过我贝蒂阿姨的家
Though I did hear you paid a visit to my aunt betty.
我不是十分喜欢贝蒂阿姨
I don't much like aunt betty.
你什么时候才能不试着笼络我的亲戚们?
when you gonna stop tryin' to win over my relations?
我只关心一个人
only one I care about,
你的堂妹罗斯安娜 我孩子的妈妈
Your cousin roseanna, mother of my baby.
小萨拉・伊丽莎白体弱多病
little sarah elizabeth is frail and ailing,
罗斯安娜也是如此
And so is roseanna.
他们说孩子活不了多久了
Folks don't expect the child to live much longer.
我真的很抱歉 约翰斯
I'm truly sorry, johnse.
如果失去孩子 恐怕你也会失去罗斯安娜
Without the baby, I fear you'll lose roseanna too.
在经历这些种种以后 我...
After all that happened, I...
似乎她也不愿意再见你了
It seems like she don't want you anymore.
我到底应该怎么做?
what am I supposed to do?
你不应该承受这些痛苦的 约翰斯
you don't deserve these hard times, johnse.
你真的不应受这些
You truly don't.
哈!
hah!
吁 吁 吁
Ho, ho, ho.
治安法官
女士请...
My lady...
沃尔叔叔
Uncle wall,
希望您能批准我和南茜・麦考伊
I'd like you to marry us,
结为夫妻
Me and nancy mccoy.
万能的上帝啊 孩子
Jesus h. Christ almighty, boy.
你彻底疯了吗?
You gone plumb crazy?
不 我没疯
no, sir.
另一个怀着你孩子的麦考伊家的女人怎么办?
what about the mccoy woman you already knocked up?
毋庸置疑 那是一段不堪回首的往事
yes, sir, well, that is a sad chapter.
虽然不是我所愿...
That seems over with...roseanna,
但我和罗斯安娜似乎已经结束了
though, not by my choosin'.
但南茜的情况就截然不同
You know, it's different with nancy.
没人会反对
There ain't no one opposed.
你父母知道吗?
Do your ma and pa know?
这回我不会再询问他们的意见了
You know, I ain't askin' this time.
求您了 沃尔叔叔
Please, uncle wall.
与麦考伊家族的联姻 对于了断
Me marrying a mccoy could help end
两个家族间的恩怨将会有益无害
All this dying between our families.
根据西弗吉尼亚州赋予我的权力
By the power vested in me by the state of west virginia,
现在我宣布你俩结成夫妇
I now pronounce you man and wife.
杰弗逊 过来把这个签了
Jefferson, come over here and sign this thing.
签在这
Right there.
让我来
Let me sign.
闭嘴
Shut up.
你真的要这样做吗 姐姐?
You sure you want to do this, sis?
小姐 笑一下吧
Smile, little lady.
今天是你大喜之日
It's your wedding day.
我们现在是夫妻了
Man and wife now.
希望我们能永远相濡以沫
And I expect no more trouble between us, not ever.
我真心希望你知道自己在干嘛 孩子
I sure hope you know what you're doin', boy.
我不知道这事要怎么开口 但我还是得说
I don't know how to tell y'all this but just say it.
有话直说 沃尔
Just come on out with it, wall.
昨天我批准了约翰斯与南茜的婚事
Yesterday I married johnse and nancy mccoy.
什么?
What?
你批准了?
You married 'em?
其实我真的很不情愿
Well, it was damn sure reluctantly.
这点我可以向你们表明
I can tell you that.
哈蒙・麦考伊的女儿?
Harmon mccoy's daughter?
哦 天哪
Oh, my god.
上次我们没答应他就没结成
Well, he was lookin' to be lost to us.
这回 他成功了
This time, he just may have succeeded.
昂斯 他认为这种方式
Well, anse, he thinks it'll make peace
可以化解你与兰德尔之间的恩怨
Between you and randall.
是吗?
He does, huh?
有谁可以告诉我 我的儿子是怎么
Somebody want to tell me how a son of mine
会他妈的变成一个白痴的?
Could turn out to be so goddamn dumb?
盖
Cap.
什么事?
Yeah?
骑上你的马
Get your horse.
去把你哥带回来
Go fetch your brother.
不管你怎么加强这个地方的防卫 昂斯
No matter how you fortify it, anse,
这里离拖轮河太近 而且毫无遮掩
This place is too close to the tug and open to attack.
只要那个该死的佩里・克莱因
As long as that peckerwood perry cline
不断增加悬赏金
keeps putting up bounties,
贪婪之士就会纷拥而至
the wolves are just gonna keep on comin'.
沃尔 看来得告诉肯塔基州的人
Oh, wall, I think we sent kentucky a notion
我们是如何处置这些赏金猎手的
of how we deal with bounty hunters.
去你的 吉姆
Damn it, jim.
我是说你们最好躲在深山老林里
All I'm sayin' is, y'all would be better off
别惹是生非了
Deeper in the mountains.
安全为重 昂斯
Just to be safe, anse.
知道了 我会按你的意思来 沃尔
Well, I'll take it under advisement, wall.
别让约翰斯把那个麦考伊的贱人一起带来
And don't you let johnse bring his new mccoy hussy with him.
我会把他带回来的 妈妈
I'll bring him home, mama.
你在跟我做那事的时候
When you do the trick with me,
你是不是幻想着罗斯安娜?
Are you picturing roseanna?
我试着不去想
Tryin' not to.
但依然无法抹去?
Tryin' but failin'?
我想我需要更多的时间
I need more time, I guess.
我等你 约翰斯
I'll give you time, johnse.
为了得到我想要的东西我可以等很久
I can wait a long time for what I want.
里面到底有没有人?
Anybody the hell in there?
那是我弟弟
That's my brother.
杰弗逊
Jefferson.
你得把我藏起来
You got to hide me.
我们为什么要这样做?
Why we got to do that?
不能让他们把我绞死 姐姐
Can't let me hang, sis,
我完全不记得我打过一场架
Not for no fight that I can't even remembers,
我当时醉了
'cause I was drunk
我对不起可怜的弗雷德・沃尔福德
And feels terrible about poor fred wolford.
弗雷德・沃尔福德?
Fred wolford?
那个邮递员
The mailman.
我们在一个谷仓舞会
We was at a barn dance,
喝酒 争论 回敬对方
Drinking, arguing, went out back,
然后就是一场混战
Commenced to scuffle.
我只是...我只是用刀稍微划了他一下
I just give him...I give him a little cut,
他却要开枪毙了我
And he tried to shoot me.
于是我就把枪转了个方向
So I wrenched that gun around,
让他朝自己开了一枪
And I made him shoot his own damn self.
惨了
Oh, hell.
今早他人就死了
He died this morning.
现在他们在到处找我
Now they all out there looking for me.
还悬了赏
They got a reward out.
过来 弟弟
Come here, brother.
你会没事的
You gonna be all right.
好吧
All right.
留下来吃饭吧 你今晚可以在这里过夜
We'll feed you. You can spend the night here.
杰弗逊 没人会找到这里
You're gonna be safe here, jefferson.
就一晚
For the night.
只要我在这他就可以待在这
As long as I'm here.
现在的我
I don't look like
已经不像当初和约翰斯在一起的我了
the girl johnse romanced no more.
我现在这个样子他还会要我吗?
Will he still want me lookin' like this?
现在才来担心这个 为时已晚
Too late to worry about that.
我本不想趟这趟浑水
I didn't want to stir the pot,
但你应该知道
But here it is.
约翰斯一走了之还结了婚
Johnse's gone and got himself married
跟你堂姐南茜
To your cousin nancy.
你听到我说的话吗?
Did you hear me?
约翰斯・哈特菲尔德
Johnse Hatfield
娶了南茜・麦考伊
Married nancy mccoy.
菲利普斯先生 很高兴见到你
mr. Phillips, good to see you.
我也很高兴见到你俩
Equally good to see the two of you.
你应该知道今早我为什么
Expect you know why I called this meeting
要在这里举行这个会议
here this morning.
你们在找解决河对岸事务
Y'all are lookin' for someone to lead a posse
的武装队队长
across the river,
而我是这方圆几十里唯一的职业杀手
And I'm the only gun handler around here
没有人能比我更胜任这份工作了
Who's man enough for the job.
为此你感到罪孽深重 不是吗?
You're awful full of yourself, ain't ya?
我不会这么认为
I wouldn't call it that.
在虚度光阴的少年时代
I wasted some years of my misspent youth
我曾跟着杰西和弗兰克跑来跑去
A'ridin' with jesse and frank.
有次我亲眼看见疯子比尔杀人
Once got to witness wild bill kill a man,
所以我见过更好的
So I seen better than me,
不过不多
Though not many.
况且你们选谁也不是我能决定的
And I can't help but see what you got to choose from.
我不知道你还有段无法无天的过去
I didn't realize you'd once been an outlaw.
哦 你当然不知道 那都是我被救之前的事了
Oh, that, of course, was before I was saved,
依靠耶和华的圣血和救世主的宽恕
Long prior to my being washed clean of sin
一直以来我都在清洗我曾经的罪孽
By the blood of our lord and savior jesus christ.
你的行为可不是基督徒风范
You sure don't act christian.
我是上帝的战士 麦考伊先生
I'm a warrior for god, mr. Mccoy,
邪恶战士
A fighter of evil,
我时刻准备着为你们捉拿那些可恨的杀人犯
Right and ready to take on your demon murderers.
我听说你还是个私家侦探
I heard you were a pinkerton man.
曾经是
I was,
直到哈特菲尔德家的人暗地里朝我开了一枪
Till I got shot in the back by hatfields,
我就成了瘸子
Left me with my limp,
这是另一个我渴望得到这份工作的原因
Another reason that warrants my hiring.
我个人也对恶魔昂斯・哈特菲尔德
I bear devil anse hatfield
和他的所有血亲心存怨恨
and all his kin a personal grudge.
让我把这理清了
Now, let me get this straight.
兰德尔想通过他们的州长
Now, randall wants his governor
让我们的州长逮捕我们
to make our governor arrest us
再把我们交给肯塔基州处置?
And cart us over to kentucky?
这叫引渡 伊莱亚斯
It's called extradition, elias,
我不相信我们的威尔逊州长会同意
And I don't think our governor wilson will agree to it.
在这场游戏中我还握着一张王牌
well, I got my own ace in this poker game.
我的老友约翰・弗洛伊德
My friend john floyd
现在在首都与文迪共事
works with windy at the capital now.
我们的新任助理国务卿
Yes, sir, our new assistant secretary of state.
约翰可以帮忙搞定
John will help out.
是盖和约翰斯
It's cap and johnse.
这孩子我们该怎么办 莉瓦西?
How do we handle this boy, 'vicy?
总不能牛不喝水强按头
Well, not by pushin' and pullin' him.
正因如此他才会投入另一个麦考伊女人的怀抱
That's what drove him into the arms of another mccoy.
你想解开这个结...
You want to untie this knot...
你就得让她恨他
You get her to hate him.
进屋就把帽子脱了
Take your hat off in here.
嗯...做丈夫感觉怎样?
So... how's the married man?
还过得去 沃尔叔叔 还行
Doin' just fine, uncle wall, just fine.
婚姻生活还是挺适合你嘛
So marriage suits you then, huh?
是啊 适合极了
Yes, sir, right down to the ground.
她做饭肯定不咋地
She must be one sorry-ass cook.
你选了个中看不中用的麦考伊新娘
You choosin' a ham supper over a comely mccoy bride.
她不再姓麦考伊
She ain't mccoy no more, is she?
她姓哈特菲尔德 约翰斯・哈特菲尔德太太
She's hatfield, mrs. Johnse hatfield.
哈特菲尔德不仅仅是一个名字
Hatfield ain't just a name on a piece of paper.
别妄想像上次那个女孩那样把她带过来
Don't expect to bring her around here like the last one.
有些事不能被麦考伊家的人听到
Things get spoke that ain't for mccoy ears.
我这不没把她带来吗?
Well, I didn't bring her here, did I?
不准对你父亲无礼
Don't sass your father.
你那浪荡的性情
Your horndog philanderin'
也为如今的混乱局面出了一份力
helped make this mess.
妈妈 求您别说了 在家时我已经受够气了
mama, please, you know what? I get enough grief at home.
说真的 我得出来透透气
Truth be told, I need to get away for a bit.
不是她的原因
It ain't her, you know.
南茜待我挺好的
Nancy treats me fine.
只是...
It's just...
她那该死的弟弟把我的蜜月搅合成了一场噩梦
Her gol'dang brother is turning my honeymoon into misery.
杰弗逊・麦考伊?
jefferson mccoy?
我听说他那天干掉了一个邮递员
I heard he killed the mailman the other day.
还设了悬赏金呢
Got a gol'dang reward up too.
你收留了一个被通缉的麦考伊家的人?
You're harborin' a mccoy with a price on his head?
南茜说是暂时的
Nancy says it's just for a while,
还说自己有保护他的义务
Says it's her duty to protect him.
这姐姐不错
Well, loyal sis.
赏金有多少?
How much is the reward?
不知道
I don't know.
一百美元吧
$100 maybe.
孩子 我们只想你幸福
Well, we just want you to be happy, son.
要不你离开家一段时间吧 好吗?
Why don't you take a little time away from home, hmm?
对谁都好
Wouldn't hurt none.
跟你爸爸出去打打猎
Go huntin' with your pa.
那倒是真的 我也挺久没打猎了
It's true. I ain't been huntin' for a spell.
你有兴趣跟我一起去吗 约翰斯?
You up to goin' with me, johnse?
听上去不错
That'd be nice.
我不确定 可能会去吧
I don't know. Yeah, might as well.
该死 总比看着我的懒汉小舅子
Shit, better than watching my layabout brother-in-law
喝光我的威士忌好 对吧?
Drink up all my whiskey profits, right?
赞成
Amen to that.
我想你就是杰弗逊・麦考伊
I believe that's a jefferson mccoy.
谁在说话?
who's sayin' that?
约翰斯・哈特菲尔德的叔叔吉姆・万斯
Johnse hatfield's uncle jim vance
还有他的弟弟盖
And his little brother cap.
在哪...约翰斯在哪里?
where's...where's johnse?
跟他的爸爸打猎去了
out huntin' with his pa.
你们来干嘛?
so what you doin' here?
我们也来打点猎
Doin' a little hunting ourselves.
呃...这附近并没有什么猎物
well... not much huntin' around here.
这个地方的鹿什么的全都被打光了
Place is all shot out of deer and such.
哦 这里还是有一些小畜生的
oh, there's still critters here.
特别是有一个小畜生
And one critter in particular
顶着一个价值可观的脑袋
Has a handsome reward on his head.
南茜!
nancy!
你们对我弟弟做了什么?
what are you doing to my brother?
南茜, 救我! 他们要把我抓起来
nancy, do something! They gonna take me in!
放开他!
get off!
回你的小木屋 麦考伊小姐
you get back in that cabin, miss mccoy.
然后回去穿好衣服
You get yourself dressed proper.
放开他 你这老白痴!
get off him, you old coot!
不放你又能怎样?
what the hell you gonna do?
南茜！
nancy!
该死
Damn it.
给你点颜色看看
I'll show you.
使劲
come on.
放倒他 南茜!
get 'em, nancy!
放开我 你...
Get off me, you...
你个婊子!
you bitch!
你个廉价的婊子!
You good for nothing bitch!
放开!
let go!
你想玩鞭子游戏?
you want to do some whippin'?
那就尝尝鞭子的味道 小妞
Here's some whippin', girl.
别让他打你!
don't let him do that to you!
是的 我猜你喜欢这样
yeah, bet you like that,
不是吗 你这卑鄙的小...
don't you, you mean little...
放开她 万斯!
get off of her, vance!
住手 吉姆
stop it, jim.
他跑了
he's gettin' away.
快点 盖
come on, cap.
别让他逃了
We're gonna lose him.
帮我稳住
stabilize me.
我没被淹死!
I ain't drowned!
快点
come on.
你们这些哈特菲尔德家的笨蛋!
you hatfield morons!
来抓我啊!
Come and get me!
该死的独眼龙!
Goddang pecker-pullers!
你们怎么了?
What's the matter with you?
不会游泳吗?
Can't swim?
来啊 开枪啊 你这半瞎的混蛋!
Go ahead, shoot, you fog-eyed, half-blind bastard!
我在这里!
Here I am!
独眼大猩猩 这可有半英里呢!
You one-eyed ape, it's 1/2 mile!
耶!
yeah!
正中脑门
A hole in the head.
干得好 孩子
you did good, boy.
南茜?
nancy?
天呐
Jesus.
有人打了你?
Somebody bashed you?
哦 天哪
Oh, my god.
吉姆・万斯把我当畜生一样打
jim vance beat me like I was a mule,
甚至连畜生都不如
worse.
吉姆叔叔?
uncle jim?
他对我施暴
he did disgusting things to me.
他和盖来这里带走了杰弗逊
Him and cap come in here and take jefferson.
现在 你告诉我实话 你做了什么
Now, you tell me true whether you had anything
才发生了这样的事
To do with that.
我向你发誓我没有
I swear to you I didn't.
南茜 我发誓
Nancy, I swear it.
好 那你快去 快去追他们
well, then you go, and you get after 'em,
然后把我的弟弟带回来
And you bring my brother back here.
你快点去
You go on and do that.
你为了我快去
You do that for me.
该死
damn it.
快点!
get!
我不能 南茜
I can't, nance.
不能 还是不愿意?
can't or you won't?
我不能
I can't.
已经太晚了
It's already been played out.
我在路上看见我...我弟弟盖
I seen my...my brother cap down the road.
杰弗逊想要逃跑
Jefferson tried to run.
盖不得不对他开枪
Cap had to shoot him.
杰弗逊已经死了 南茜
jefferson's killed, nancy.
哦
oh.
不 所有人都离开了我
No. Now I ain't got no one.
嘿 嘿 嘿
hey, hey, hey.
他们全死了
all of 'em dead.
现在我一无所有了
Now I ain't got nobody.
现在我弟弟也死了
Now my brother's dead.
你还有我
you got me.
- 你还有...- 不!
- You st... - no!
- 你还有我 - 滚开 该死的!
- you still got me. - stop it, damn it!
- 过来 - 别碰我!
- come here. - don't touch me!
别闹了!
Stop it!
你给我滚!
I don't want you here!
不!
No!
嘿
hey.
不
no.
No.
该死
Damn it.
滚出去
Get out of here.
滚!
Get!
滚出去!
Get out of here!
为什么你想加入武装队?
why you want to be on the posse?
我不喜欢哈特菲尔德家的人
I don't like hatfields.
你当过兵吗?
were you in the army?
我南北军队都报过名
I tried to enlist, both sides.
我的生殖器有点问题
There was something awry with my genitals.
所以你不能骑马?
it prevent you from riding a horse?
哦 现在可以了
oh, not anymore.
而且我枪法还不错
And I'm a fine shot.
我可以打中四十码外的老鼠屁股
I can hit a rat's ass at 40 yards.
把你的地址留下 到时候会找你
you leave word where to find you when it comes to that.
下一个
Next.
我叫兰塞姆・布雷
my name is ransom bray.
我参过军 也能骑马
I am armed and ready to ride.
我会投入战斗 完成你交给我的
And I'll take on your fight and anyone or anything
一切任务
You put in front of me.
菲利普斯先生 我要加入武装队
Mr. Phillips, I ain't here to just join a posse.
我想做你的副手
I want to be your personal deputy,
因为我肯干 我不会说...
'cause I work hard, and I wouldn't say...
有任何法律实施方面的经验吗?
got any law enforcement experience?
呃 我...我愿意学习
well, I...I want to learn the occupation,
因为我知道我会胜任的
'cause I know I'd be good at it.
我不是在胡说
I ain't gonna give you no guff.
好吧 听着 只要你让我进
All right, look, you take me on,
我甚至可以把我的薪水分给你
And I'll even split my wages with you.
好吧 先生
well, sir,
让我跟克莱因先生和麦考伊先生商量一下
Let me talk to mr. Cline and mr. Mccoy about you.
楼上有位女士想要跟你谈谈
lady upstairs wanting to talk to you.
先生们 我马上回来
gentlemen, I'll be back.
楼下有个男人说你有话要对我说
Man downstairs said you had something to tell me.
你想知道塞尔柯克・麦考伊在哪里吗?
how would you like to know where selkirk mccoy is,
那个杀死自己亲戚的叛徒?
Traitor that killed his own kin?
交换条件是什么?
what would you want in return?
条件是杀掉吉姆・万斯
for you to kill jim vance,
那个让我的脸变成这样的人...
man that did this to my face...
更重要的是 他杀了我的弟弟和我爸爸
Worse than that, killed my brother and my pap.
吉姆・万斯本来就在名单上
jim vance is on the list.
我们早晚会抓住他们每一个人
Sooner or later we gonna get every damn one.
不仅仅要抓住他们 还要杀了他们
not just get 'em, kill 'em.
你可以在塞尔柯克身上做示范
You can demonstrate on selkirk.
他更名改姓在贝克利维尔工作
He's workin' down in beckleyville using a fake name.
要我也杀了他?
want me to kill him too?
我不在乎这个
makes me no never mind.
我只恨吉姆・万斯
It's jim vance I hate.
还有另一件事情
And just one other thing.
让约翰斯・哈特菲尔德...
Just leave johnse hatfield be...
暂时活着
For now.
准备?
ready?
起
Up.
塞尔柯克・麦考伊 杀了自己亲戚的人
selkirk mccoy, the kin killer.
是的 先生 我想就是你
Yes, sir, I believe that's you.
呃 你认错人了 先生
well, you got me wrong, sir.
我的名字是比德韦尔
Name's bidwell.
别放狗屁了
stop the horseshit.
你就是塞尔柯克・麦考伊 我们都知道
You're selkirk mccoy, and we damn well know it.
别...别杀我
don't...don't kill me.
别杀我 我投降
Don't kill me. I give up.
我投降 我乖乖跟你走
I give up. You got me dead to rights.
一个能杀死自己堂兄弟的人
a man who'd shoot his own cousins,
我可不信他会乖乖被我们活捉
I don't expect he'd let himself get taken alive.
你就继续演吧
Make your play.
我没带枪
I ain't wearin' no gun.
我手举高
My hands are up.
我不会剥夺一个人自我防卫的权利
I won't deny a man his right to defend hisself.
我数到五 你就去死吧
I'll count to five, and you go for it.
一 二...
One, two...
亚伦 你告诉他我投降了!
aaron, you tell him I'll surrender!
三
three.
我趴下
I'm gettin' down on the floor.
我没用 我投降
I'm helpless. I surrender.
这里有目击者
You got a witness right there.
他知道我已经投降了
He knows I give myself up.
加略人犹大出卖了耶稣
是的 真实的加略人犹大
yeah, real-life judas iscariot.
别开枪 先生
don't do it, mister.
这是不对的
It ain't right.
也许你是对的
maybe you're right.
他也许还不值一颗子弹的钱
Maybe he ain't worth the price of a bullet.
是的 我不值 先生
That's right. No, sir.
出击吧 盖
hit me, cap.
哦
Ooh.
是我
it's me.
把这该死的门打开
Open the damn door.
他一个人
he's alone.
嘿 甜心
hey, sugar.
你疯了吗 孩子?
you insane, boy?
干得好 约翰斯 别停手
that's right, johnse. Don't give up.
喔
Whoa.
加油 约翰斯
Come on, johnse.
- 好! - 你闭嘴
- yeah! - you shut up.
你为什么要那样做 吉姆叔叔?
why'd you do it, uncle jim?
我他妈到底做了什么? 什么?
what the hell? Do what?
快上 盖
get your money, cap.
把他们拉开
let's get 'em.
够了 住手
all right, now.
放开他
Get off him.
我要宰了你!
I'm gonna kill you!
你个魔鬼!
You monster!
南茜说你他妈的差点强暴了她!
Nancy says you damn near raped her!
她胡说!
that's a lie!
是那个婊子先冲过来的
That bitch came at me first.
你说的是我妻子 嘴巴放干净点
that's my wife you're talking about, god damn it.
约翰斯 坐下
johnse, sit down.
你喝高了
You're drunk.
来 坐下
Sit, sit.
也只有喝多了 我才有勇气来这里
the only way I could come here was liquored up.
你以为我他妈愿意这样对待我的家人
I hate goin' up against my family like this.
吉姆叔叔说的对 是南茜先动手的
uncle jim's right about nancy comin' after him.
他先拿起牛鞭打他的
She started whippin' him with a cow's tail.
她差点弄瞎我的眼睛
pret'near took my eye out, she did.
为了保命 我才不得已夺下她的鞭子
I had to jerk that thing out of her hand to save myself.
抱歉 约翰斯
I'm sorry, johnse.
好吧...你知道的
Well...you know.
你听说塞尔柯克的事了吗?
you hear about selkirk?
那个恶人弗兰克把他送进了派克维尔监狱
That bad frank prick hauled him off to pikeville jail.
他是怎么知道他藏身之处的 约翰斯?
how did he know where he was, johnse?
塞尔柯克已经隐姓埋名了
Selkirk was incognito.
只有哈特菲尔德的人才知道他在哪
Only us hatfields knew where he was.
我是个不折不扣的哈特菲尔德人
I am foursquare hatfield,
从身到心 从生至死
Front and back, dawn to dusk.
是啊 所以脾气那么暴躁
yeah, well, that's why emotions are runnin' so wild,
我们中间有奸细
Because there's a spy amongst us.
吁
whoa.
文件通过了
Papers come through.
官方文件
It's official.
嗯
Mmn
"肯塔基州 特别代表"
"Special deputy, state of kentucky,"
"弗兰克・菲利普斯先生"
"Mr. Frank phillips."
州长西蒙・巴克纳寄
Sent by governor simon buckner.
你应该很高兴吧 菲利普斯先生
you should be very pleased, mr. Phillips.
各位 如果遇到反击
Men, should you meet resistance,
不到必要的时候 不要动用武力
You'll use no more force than is necessary to prevail.
毕竟我们不是哈特菲尔德那样的异教徒
We are not infidels like the hatfields.
我们要依法行事
We embody the law.
我们来祈祷
Let us pray.
亲爱的上帝
Dear lord,
愿您与我们同在 保佑我们的勇士
May you be with us today and bless our endeavors.
阿门
Amen.
多年前 是你带领大家
years past, you'd have lead the charge
收拾了烂摊子
And fixed this mess yourself.
现在 还是让我们年轻人来做吧
Today you best leave it to the younger men.
他杀死了我的儿子们
he killed my boys.
这是我的战斗
This is my fight.
你的儿子们可以代替你
your sons can ride in your stead.
体体面面地 麦考伊先生 卸任吧
With dignified regard, mr. Mccoy, you ain't deputized.
他说的对 兰德尔
he's right, randall.
你总是坚持要依法行事
You're the one who insists this all be legal.
好吧
yah.
我们出发!
let's ride!
孩子们不会有事的
our boys will be fine.
我以为你会和他们一起去
I thought you were goin' off with 'em.
嗯 他们觉得我老了 不中用了
mm, they reckon I'm too old and shaky.
会他们拖后腿
I'd slow 'em down.
他们还年轻
They're young men.
我们祈祷他们平安吧
We should pray for their safety.
你还没厌倦祈祷这回事吗 兰德尔?
you ever get tired of praying, randall?
好像也很少管用
Seems like it so rarely works.
我们不应该怀疑上帝的旨意
it's not ours to question god's will.
我们应该信仰上帝的旨意
That's what faith's for.
不要害怕 孩子他妈
Don't be fearful, mother.
林子一片漆黑的时候真是渗人
gets awful dark in these woods at night.
我们可以用一些托马斯・爱迪生发明的
We could use some of tom edison's
电灯泡
Electric lightnin' bulbs.
我想给你的太多
there's so much I wanted to give you,
太多 莎莉
So much, sally.
但是此生带给你的却只有痛苦
But all I brought you is pain in this life.
是其他人造成的 不是你
others have, but not you.
你总是相信一切你所说 兰德尔
You always believe what you say, randall.
难得的品质 我欣赏你这一点
That is a rare quality, and I admire you for it.
这就是你嫁给我的原因吗?
that why you married me?
我嫁给你 是因为有一天
I married you, because one day,
你会给我买那个双层电锅
You're gonna buy me that electric double boiler.
守卫去哪了?
where's the guards?
不知道
I don't know.
或许在等着伏击我们呢
Maybe waiting to ambush us.
一个人都没有 菲利普斯先生
there ain't nobody here, mr. Phillips.
食物还在炉子上 桌子上还摆着盘子
food on the stove, plates on the table.
我们等他们回来吧
Let's wait till they get back.
恶魔他不会回来了
devil ain't comin' back.
听到我们要来的风声 早躲到深山里去了
Heard us comin' and gone deep in the hills.
除非在他逃跑路上抓住他
Least we got him on the run.
现在 我们得去抓别的人
Now, we got others to go fetch.
起床了 弗伦奇 你个懒货
Wake up, frenchy, you lazy son of a bitch.
别踢我 拉克 贱人
don't kick me, lark, you asshole.
拉克・瓦尼!
lark varney!
弗伦奇・埃利斯!
French ellis!
快点滚出来!
Come on outside!
就留你们一条狗命!
We'll give you one chance!
你是谁?
well, who are you?
派克县的代理执法官!
Deputy marshals out of pike county!
派克县位于肯塔基州 南界西维吉尼亚州
我们手握逮捕令!
We got warrants!
放下武器 举手投降!
Toss out your guns and come on out!
我们在追捕恶魔昂斯・哈特菲尔德!
We're lookin' for Devil Anse Hatfield!
你们这些蠢货知不知道他在哪里?
Either one of you mush-heads know where he went to?
嘿 是你么 兰塞姆・布雷?
Hey, that you, Ransom Bray?
嘿 我认识你!
Hey, I know you!
上次把你妹妹露丝安妮背回家的
Yeah, I'm friends with the fella that's humpin' your sister
那个哥们是我朋友!
Ruth-Anne back home!
我本来想亲自照顾她的
Thought maybe I'd look her up myself,
但是路途实在过于遥远!
but the line's too long!
啊!
Ah!
我想他们打中我了 弗伦奇
I think they killed me, frenchy.
我...我中枪了
I'm g... I'm gutshot.
告诉我们哈特菲尔德一伙逃向哪里
Tell us where the Hatfields run off to,
就放你们一马!
and we'll spare you!
- 嘿 拉克 - 快点投降!
- Hey, Lark. - Come on out!
他们打中我了 弗伦奇
They shot me, frenchy.
坚持住 喝点这个
Come on. Drink some of this.
我会陪在你身边的 拉克
You got to stay with me, Lark.
我会带你逃出去的
Okay, I'm freightin' you out.
- 好的 - 好吗?
- Okay. - Okay?
好的
Okay.
你掩护我 然后我趁机抛开
You put up a good show, and I'll make a run for it,
从后面包抄他们
circle behind 'em.
- 好吗? - 好的 快点
- Okay. - Okay, come on.
跟我来
Come on.
好吧 我们出来了
All right, we're comin'.
停止射击
Hold your fire.
拉克会告诉你们有关哈特菲尔德一伙人的下落
Lark will tell you about the Hatfields.
那么 你在右边吸引他们注意
All right, you break to the right,
我从左边跑 好吗?
and I'll go left, okay?
听着 我投降!
All right, I quit this fight!
我放下武器!
Here's my gun!
早知道你们都会来的话
Hell, if I'd have known y'all was comin',
我一定穿上我最好的衣服
I'd have put my Sunday best on.
弗伦奇 你被逮捕了 因为涉嫌
French, you're under arrest for your part
参与谋杀兰德尔・麦考伊的儿子们
in the illegal execution of the sons of Randall McCoy.
你是怎么认识我的妹妹露丝安妮的?
How you know my sister Ruth-Anne?
麦考伊兄弟们
McCoy boys.
卡尔文 吉姆
Calvin, Jim,
看来你们都被迫卷入了你们爸爸的战争
I see y'all were takin' up your daddy's war.
天啊 你已经抓住亚历克斯和查理了?
Jesus, you already got Alex and Charlie?
另外一些人我不认识
You know, that other fella I don't recognize.
所以你们是遇到谁就抓吗?
I mean, y'all just round up anybody you come across?
你只需知道
All you need to know is,
逮捕令上面有你的名字
this here warrant has your name on it.
好吧 看来我会被处以绞刑
Yeah, reckon I'm gonna hang,
对于我的家族来说 将会是一个莫大的遗憾
be a big disappointment to my family.
直接带我们去恶魔昂斯那里
Well, take us straightaway to Devil Anse,
你就不需要被关在笼子里面了
you won't have to ride in the cage.
你是怎么认识我妹妹的?
How do you know my sister?
去过布鲁菲尔德的人
Hell, everybody pass through bluefield
谁没有跟露丝安妮・布鲁做过皮肉生意呢
gets a pork job from Ruth-Anne Bray.
他妈的在做什么?
What the hell?
他就是闭不上他的狗嘴
Made one damn remark too many.
他要带我们去找恶魔昂斯!
He was takin' us to Devil Anse!
他根本不知道哈特菲尔德在哪!
He don't know where Hatfield is!
弗伦奇・埃利斯就是个满口谎话的大骗子
French Ellis was always a fat liar.
你怎么认识他的?
How do you know him?
我在学校度过的唯一一年时光 他是我同学
We was in school together, the one year I went.
我解雇白痴的方法就是
The way I fire asswipe morons is,
把子弹射入他们的猪脑中
I put a bullet in their goddamn heads.
我保证下不为例
Won't happen again.
抱歉
Apologize.
我们必须立刻出发
We got to do this right.
谨慎行事!
Politic!
不得违抗命令 听清楚了吗?
No more trail justice, you hear?
今天我就是警长
I might want to be sheriff one day.
嘿
Hey.
我把弹药和温切斯特步枪带来了
I picked up our ammo and our winchesters.
很好
Good.
愚蠢的麦考伊家族的人只顾着攻击推船
Dumb McCoy's raiding all the push boats;
却忘记了邮车这回事
Didn't think to check the mail wagon.
- 是的 - 是真的吗?
- Yeah. - Is it true?
威尔逊州长在这里?
Governor Wilson in there?
下一个好消息是
Next best thing.
他把约翰・B・弗洛伊德派来了
He sent his boy John B. Floyd.
不 不 不
No, no, no.
约翰 此时此刻 我希望你能明白
John, now, I want you to understand this.
我们目前情况是 拉克・瓦尼
Now, what we got here is Lark Varney,
弗伦奇・埃利斯和臭鼬头华莱士
French Ellis, Skunkhair Wallace,
都已经死了
all of them dead.
然后亚历克斯・梅塞尔 塞尔柯克...
Then we got Alex Messer, Selkirk...
这些软弱的人...
pliant men...
大约有六个被绑架了
about a half dozen others kidnapped.
我知道了 沃尔
I hear you, Wall.
真不知道我们会有多少亲属
It's hard to know how many of our relations
就这样死无葬身之地
they've buried in unmarked graves.
为什么会这样
Why,
你有威尔逊州长的大力支持啊 昂斯
you have governor Wilson's complete support, Anse.
他已经竭尽全力了
He's doin' everything he can.
那么 只能说他做的还不够
Well, it's pretty clear it ain't enough.
我已经为你们被囚禁的公民
I petitioned the U.S. district court
向美国地方法院申请了人身保护令
for writs of habeas corpus on our imprisoned citizens.
如今 威尔逊州长和巴克纳州长
Now, governor Wilson has had a heated exchange
在电报中已经激烈交锋了
of telegrams with governor Buckner.
激烈交锋?
Heated exchange?
是的 先生
Yes, sir.
听到了吗 沃尔? 他们...
Hear that, Wall? They had a...
他们激烈交锋了
They had themselves a heated exchange.
嗯
Mm.
把边境警卫交给我 约翰
Give me troopers at the border, John,
边境警卫
troopers at the border,
那样的话 当麦考伊挑衅的话
so when McCoy tries it again,
你就可以狠狠回击他了
you stop his ass.
约翰 约翰 这些混蛋干的都是非法的事
John, John, what these son' bitches are doin' is illegal.
其他州的执法官没有权力
Ain't no out-of-state lawman got the right to invade
入侵另一个主权州并且绑架其公民
another sovereign state to abduct citizens,
不管有没有该死的逮捕令
warrant or no damn warrant.
我向肯塔基州递交了一份官方申请书
I sent an official requisition to Kentucky
要求逮捕弗兰克・菲利普斯
calling for the arrest of Frank Phillips
以及他武装队中二十三名成员
and 23 members of his posse.
肯塔基州不会采取任何行动
Kentucky ain't gonna do nothin'.
但如果他们再次企图入侵西弗吉尼亚州的话
But if they try to invade West Virginia again,
麦考伊先生手下的武装队都将被直接逮捕
Mr. McCoy's posse can be arrested here.
那么 被谁逮捕呢?
Mmhmm, by who?
该死的 快授权我们为代表
Ah, hell, deputize us.
给我们几门大炮 我们立刻骑马冲进派克维尔
Give us a few Cannon, we'll ride into Pikeville,
了结这该死的一切
end this shit right now.
先生 你所说的将挑起另一场内战
Sir, you are talkin' about startin' another civil war.
这不仅是说说而已 约翰
That's not talk, John.
这是我们下一步计划
That's what we already got.
请你转告州长...
So you tell the governor...
他不插手的话 那么就由我来代劳
He steps in, or I will.